{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946890791099","data":{"timestamp":" 946890791099"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_121301"," gameId":" 45c2f47a-bc08-416b-b328-ad4d268817e1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.reveal::100..1000.TD_OFF1_DES_RAND.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946890798568","data":{"timestamp":" 946890798567"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_121301"," gameId":" 45c2f47a-bc08-416b-b328-ad4d268817e1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946890805093","data":{"timestamp":" 946890805093"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_121301"," gameId":" 45c2f47a-bc08-416b-b328-ad4d268817e1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946890814671","data":{"timestamp":" 946890814670"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_121301"," gameId":" a7db3af1-ee21-406e-b1cb-3539fa3aaf36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946890814901","data":{"timestamp":" 946890814901"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_121301"," gameId":" a7db3af1-ee21-406e-b1cb-3539fa3aaf36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946890815135","data":{"timestamp":" 946890815135"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_121301"," gameId":" a7db3af1-ee21-406e-b1cb-3539fa3aaf36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946890815206","data":{"timestamp":" 946890815206"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_121301"," gameId":" a7db3af1-ee21-406e-b1cb-3539fa3aaf36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946890829707","data":{"timestamp":" 946890829707"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_121301"," gameId":" a7db3af1-ee21-406e-b1cb-3539fa3aaf36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.dic:WR-3D.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946890851674","data":{"timestamp":" 946890851674"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_121301"," gameId":" 7713da5d-8735-4d80-b4ad-ebc69ec21746"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.dic_WR-3D.19"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_112"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" <space>"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.dic:WR-3D.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946890853000","data":{"timestamp":" 946890852999"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_121301"," gameId":" 7713da5d-8735-4d80-b4ad-ebc69ec21746"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.dic_WR-3D.19"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_112"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" <space>"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.dic:WR-3D.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946890855813","data":{"timestamp":" 946890855813"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_121301"," gameId":" 7713da5d-8735-4d80-b4ad-ebc69ec21746"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.dic_WR-3D.19"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_112"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.dic:WR-3D.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946890857964","data":{"timestamp":" 946890857964"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_121301"," gameId":" 7713da5d-8735-4d80-b4ad-ebc69ec21746"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.dic_WR-3D.19"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_112"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" <space>"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.dic:WR-3D.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946890868290","data":{"timestamp":" 946890868290"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_121301"," gameId":" 7713da5d-8735-4d80-b4ad-ebc69ec21746"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.dic_WR-3D.19"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_681"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.dic:WR-3D.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946890873502","data":{"timestamp":" 946890873502"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_121301"," gameId":" 7713da5d-8735-4d80-b4ad-ebc69ec21746"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.dic_WR-3D.19"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_681"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.dic:WR-3D.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946890877419","data":{"timestamp":" 946890877419"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_121301"," gameId":" 7713da5d-8735-4d80-b4ad-ebc69ec21746"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.dic_WR-3D.19"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_681"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.dic:WR-3D.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946890879226","data":{"timestamp":" 946890879226"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_121301"," gameId":" 7713da5d-8735-4d80-b4ad-ebc69ec21746"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.dic_WR-3D.19"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_681"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" <space>"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.dic:WR-3D.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946890884541","data":{"timestamp":" 946890884541"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_121301"," gameId":" 7713da5d-8735-4d80-b4ad-ebc69ec21746"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.dic_WR-3D.19"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_681"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.dic:WR-3D.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946890886399","data":{"timestamp":" 946890886399"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_121301"," gameId":" 7713da5d-8735-4d80-b4ad-ebc69ec21746"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.dic_WR-3D.19"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_681"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" <space>"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.dic:WR-3D.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946890891770","data":{"timestamp":" 946890891770"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_121301"," gameId":" 7713da5d-8735-4d80-b4ad-ebc69ec21746"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.dic_WR-3D.19"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_681"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.dic:WR-3D.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946890893743","data":{"timestamp":" 946890893743"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_121301"," gameId":" 7713da5d-8735-4d80-b4ad-ebc69ec21746"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.dic_WR-3D.19"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_681"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" <space>"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.dic:WR-3D.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946890898941","data":{"timestamp":" 946890898941"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_121301"," gameId":" 7713da5d-8735-4d80-b4ad-ebc69ec21746"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.dic_WR-3D.19"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_681"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.dic:WR-3D.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946890905704","data":{"timestamp":" 946890905704"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_121301"," gameId":" 7713da5d-8735-4d80-b4ad-ebc69ec21746"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.dic_WR-3D.19"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_681"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.dic:WR-3D.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946890914080","data":{"timestamp":" 946890914079"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_121301"," gameId":" 7713da5d-8735-4d80-b4ad-ebc69ec21746"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.dic_WR-3D.19"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_681"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946890920877","data":{"timestamp":" 946890920877"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_121301"," gameId":" 7713da5d-8735-4d80-b4ad-ebc69ec21746"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.dic_WR-3D.19"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_681"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946890928202","data":{"timestamp":" 946890928202"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_121301"," gameId":" 7713da5d-8735-4d80-b4ad-ebc69ec21746"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.dic_WR-3D.19"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_681"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946890933819","data":{"timestamp":" 946890933819"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_121301"," gameId":" 7713da5d-8735-4d80-b4ad-ebc69ec21746"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.dic_WR-3D.19"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_681"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.reveal::100..1000.TD_OFF1_DES_RAND.50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946890942290","data":{"timestamp":" 946890942290"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_121301"," gameId":" 7713da5d-8735-4d80-b4ad-ebc69ec21746"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.dic_WR-3D.19"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_681"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946890953859","data":{"timestamp":" 946890953859"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_121301"," gameId":" ef2b5fa5-c434-45ab-8a46-8af42449bf82"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946890958376","data":{"timestamp":" 946890958375"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_121301"," gameId":" ef2b5fa5-c434-45ab-8a46-8af42449bf82"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946890958473","data":{"timestamp":" 946890958473"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_121301"," gameId":" ef2b5fa5-c434-45ab-8a46-8af42449bf82"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946890964766","data":{"timestamp":" 946890964765"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_121301"," gameId":" ef2b5fa5-c434-45ab-8a46-8af42449bf82"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946890970517","data":{"timestamp":" 946890970517"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_121301"," gameId":" ef2b5fa5-c434-45ab-8a46-8af42449bf82"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:100..1000.by.within.dn.x2s.Ax.mc.80","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946890983287","data":{"timestamp":" 946890983287"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_121301"," gameId":" ef2b5fa5-c434-45ab-8a46-8af42449bf82"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946890992603","data":{"timestamp":" 946890992603"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_121301"," gameId":" ef2b5fa5-c434-45ab-8a46-8af42449bf82"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946891000140","data":{"timestamp":" 946891000139"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_121301"," gameId":" ef2b5fa5-c434-45ab-8a46-8af42449bf82"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946891005611","data":{"timestamp":" 946891005611"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_121301"," gameId":" ef2b5fa5-c434-45ab-8a46-8af42449bf82"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:100..1000.by.within.dn.x2s.Ax.mc.80","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946891014715","data":{"timestamp":" 946891014715"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_121301"," gameId":" ef2b5fa5-c434-45ab-8a46-8af42449bf82"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946891023482","data":{"timestamp":" 946891023482"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_121301"," gameId":" cfdb03ca-932e-4e1f-b8c9-2d509d4a585b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" NJAA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946891023799","data":{"timestamp":" 946891023798"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_121301"," gameId":" cfdb03ca-932e-4e1f-b8c9-2d509d4a585b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946891023887","data":{"timestamp":" 946891023887"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_121301"," gameId":" cfdb03ca-932e-4e1f-b8c9-2d509d4a585b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" NJAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946891037330","data":{"timestamp":" 946891037330"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_121301"," gameId":" ca3ea06a-999a-4ece-8503-11c37656970a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946891037554","data":{"timestamp":" 946891037554"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_121301"," gameId":" ca3ea06a-999a-4ece-8503-11c37656970a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946891038518","data":{"timestamp":" 946891038517"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_121301"," gameId":" ca3ea06a-999a-4ece-8503-11c37656970a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946891038607","data":{"timestamp":" 946891038607"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_121301"," gameId":" ca3ea06a-999a-4ece-8503-11c37656970a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946891038700","data":{"timestamp":" 946891038699"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_121301"," gameId":" ca3ea06a-999a-4ece-8503-11c37656970a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946891047886","data":{"timestamp":" 946891047886"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_121301"," gameId":" 0b1147ab-8bfa-4b7b-aa66-8a2ee0e21ad0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" START_KUBWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946891049576","data":{"timestamp":" 946891049576"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_121301"," gameId":" 0b1147ab-8bfa-4b7b-aa66-8a2ee0e21ad0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946891050664","data":{"timestamp":" 946891050664"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_121301"," gameId":" 0b1147ab-8bfa-4b7b-aa66-8a2ee0e21ad0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946891050837","data":{"timestamp":" 946891050837"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_121301"," gameId":" 0b1147ab-8bfa-4b7b-aa66-8a2ee0e21ad0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:100..1000.by.100.dn.x2s.Ax.rise.81","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946891057081","data":{"timestamp":" 946891057081"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_121301"," gameId":" 0b1147ab-8bfa-4b7b-aa66-8a2ee0e21ad0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946891062851","data":{"timestamp":" 946891062851"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_121301"," gameId":" 0b1147ab-8bfa-4b7b-aa66-8a2ee0e21ad0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946891070659","data":{"timestamp":" 946891070658"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_121301"," gameId":" 0b1147ab-8bfa-4b7b-aa66-8a2ee0e21ad0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946891082896","data":{"timestamp":" 946891082896"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_121301"," gameId":" 0b1147ab-8bfa-4b7b-aa66-8a2ee0e21ad0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:100..1000.by.100.dn.x2s.Ax.rise.81","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946891097754","data":{"timestamp":" 946891097753"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_121301"," gameId":" 0b1147ab-8bfa-4b7b-aa66-8a2ee0e21ad0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946891111713","data":{"timestamp":" 946891111713"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_121301"," gameId":" 1145d2a1-a36d-4b21-9bc3-996d177ff792"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" WAKATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946891113092","data":{"timestamp":" 946891113092"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_121301"," gameId":" 1145d2a1-a36d-4b21-9bc3-996d177ff792"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946891113309","data":{"timestamp":" 946891113309"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_121301"," gameId":" 1145d2a1-a36d-4b21-9bc3-996d177ff792"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" WAKATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946891119558","data":{"timestamp":" 946891119557"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_121301"," gameId":" 1145d2a1-a36d-4b21-9bc3-996d177ff792"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946891125743","data":{"timestamp":" 946891125743"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_121301"," gameId":" 1145d2a1-a36d-4b21-9bc3-996d177ff792"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::100..1000.TD_OFFW100_INC.26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946891132592","data":{"timestamp":" 946891132592"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_121301"," gameId":" 1145d2a1-a36d-4b21-9bc3-996d177ff792"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946891140315","data":{"timestamp":" 946891140315"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_121301"," gameId":" 1145d2a1-a36d-4b21-9bc3-996d177ff792"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946891150782","data":{"timestamp":" 946891150782"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_121301"," gameId":" 43ac2807-5e88-46e3-86f3-1b79ead48c78"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946891151012","data":{"timestamp":" 946891151012"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_121301"," gameId":" 43ac2807-5e88-46e3-86f3-1b79ead48c78"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946891151973","data":{"timestamp":" 946891151972"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_121301"," gameId":" 43ac2807-5e88-46e3-86f3-1b79ead48c78"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946891151976","data":{"timestamp":" 946891151976"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_121301"," gameId":" 43ac2807-5e88-46e3-86f3-1b79ead48c78"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946891152062","data":{"timestamp":" 946891152062"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_121301"," gameId":" 43ac2807-5e88-46e3-86f3-1b79ead48c78"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946891157539","data":{"timestamp":" 946891157539"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_121301"," gameId":" 43ac2807-5e88-46e3-86f3-1b79ead48c78"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:100..1000.by.within.dn.x2s.Ax.rise.82","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946891169729","data":{"timestamp":" 946891169728"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_121301"," gameId":" 43ac2807-5e88-46e3-86f3-1b79ead48c78"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946891175837","data":{"timestamp":" 946891175837"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_121301"," gameId":" 43ac2807-5e88-46e3-86f3-1b79ead48c78"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946891181777","data":{"timestamp":" 946891181776"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_121301"," gameId":" 43ac2807-5e88-46e3-86f3-1b79ead48c78"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946891191880","data":{"timestamp":" 946891191879"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_121301"," gameId":" 43ac2807-5e88-46e3-86f3-1b79ead48c78"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:100..1000.by.within.dn.x2s.Ax.rise.82","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946891205502","data":{"timestamp":" 946891205502"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_121301"," gameId":" cf866c80-319d-462c-a251-4da67aa22aa6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_100..1000.by.within.dn.x2s.Ax.rise.82"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_962_160-962-683"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 962"," userResponse":" 962"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:100..1000.by.within.dn.x2s.Ax.rise.82","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946891216851","data":{"timestamp":" 946891216851"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_121301"," gameId":" cf866c80-319d-462c-a251-4da67aa22aa6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_100..1000.by.within.dn.x2s.Ax.rise.82"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_802_241-683-802"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 802"," userResponse":" 802"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:100..1000.by.within.dn.x2s.Ax.rise.82","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946891229053","data":{"timestamp":" 946891229053"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_121301"," gameId":" cf866c80-319d-462c-a251-4da67aa22aa6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_100..1000.by.within.dn.x2s.Ax.rise.82"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_737_737-160-432"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 737"," userResponse":" 737"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:100..1000.by.within.dn.x2s.Ax.rise.82","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946891242569","data":{"timestamp":" 946891242569"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_121301"," gameId":" cf866c80-319d-462c-a251-4da67aa22aa6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_100..1000.by.within.dn.x2s.Ax.rise.82"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_683_683-962-432"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 683"," userResponse":" 683"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:100..1000.by.within.dn.x2s.Ax.rise.82","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946891255924","data":{"timestamp":" 946891255924"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_121301"," gameId":" cf866c80-319d-462c-a251-4da67aa22aa6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_100..1000.by.within.dn.x2s.Ax.rise.82"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_579_579-432-962"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 579"," userResponse":" 579"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:100..1000.by.within.dn.x2s.Ax.rise.82","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946891269255","data":{"timestamp":" 946891269255"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_121301"," gameId":" cf866c80-319d-462c-a251-4da67aa22aa6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_100..1000.by.within.dn.x2s.Ax.rise.82"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_432_432-579-962"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 432"," userResponse":" 432"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:100..1000.by.within.dn.x2s.Ax.rise.82","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946891283255","data":{"timestamp":" 946891283255"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_121301"," gameId":" cf866c80-319d-462c-a251-4da67aa22aa6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_100..1000.by.within.dn.x2s.Ax.rise.82"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_372_372-579-160"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 372"," userResponse":" 372"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:100..1000.by.within.dn.x2s.Ax.rise.82","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946891296280","data":{"timestamp":" 946891296279"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_121301"," gameId":" cf866c80-319d-462c-a251-4da67aa22aa6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_100..1000.by.within.dn.x2s.Ax.rise.82"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_241_372-107-241"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 241"," userResponse":" 241"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:100..1000.by.within.dn.x2s.Ax.rise.82","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946891312353","data":{"timestamp":" 946891312353"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_121301"," gameId":" cf866c80-319d-462c-a251-4da67aa22aa6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_100..1000.by.within.dn.x2s.Ax.rise.82"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_160_160-962-372"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 160"," userResponse":" 160"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:100..1000.by.within.dn.x2s.Ax.rise.82","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946891322397","data":{"timestamp":" 946891322397"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_121301"," gameId":" cf866c80-319d-462c-a251-4da67aa22aa6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_100..1000.by.within.dn.x2s.Ax.rise.82"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_107_962-107-802"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 107"," userResponse":" 107"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:100..1000.by.within.dn.x2s.Ax.rise.82","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946891327749","data":{"timestamp":" 946891327748"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_121301"," gameId":" cf866c80-319d-462c-a251-4da67aa22aa6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_100..1000.by.within.dn.x2s.Ax.rise.82"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_107_962-107-802"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946891335808","data":{"timestamp":" 946891335807"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_121301"," gameId":" cf866c80-319d-462c-a251-4da67aa22aa6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_100..1000.by.within.dn.x2s.Ax.rise.82"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_107_962-107-802"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946891344230","data":{"timestamp":" 946891344229"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_121301"," gameId":" cf866c80-319d-462c-a251-4da67aa22aa6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_100..1000.by.within.dn.x2s.Ax.rise.82"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_107_962-107-802"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946891356627","data":{"timestamp":" 946891356627"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_121301"," gameId":" cf866c80-319d-462c-a251-4da67aa22aa6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_100..1000.by.within.dn.x2s.Ax.rise.82"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_107_962-107-802"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.reveal::100..1000.TD_OFFW100_INC.53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946891366798","data":{"timestamp":" 946891366798"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_121301"," gameId":" cf866c80-319d-462c-a251-4da67aa22aa6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_100..1000.by.within.dn.x2s.Ax.rise.82"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_107_962-107-802"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946891372627","data":{"timestamp":" 946891372626"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_121301"," gameId":" cf866c80-319d-462c-a251-4da67aa22aa6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_100..1000.by.within.dn.x2s.Ax.rise.82"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_107_962-107-802"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946891382070","data":{"timestamp":" 946891382070"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_121301"," gameId":" f8fed861-c7ec-49f9-9840-55c864b6a3bc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946891382304","data":{"timestamp":" 946891382303"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_121301"," gameId":" f8fed861-c7ec-49f9-9840-55c864b6a3bc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946891383276","data":{"timestamp":" 946891383276"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_121301"," gameId":" f8fed861-c7ec-49f9-9840-55c864b6a3bc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946891384554","data":{"timestamp":" 946891384554"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_121301"," gameId":" f8fed861-c7ec-49f9-9840-55c864b6a3bc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946891385880","data":{"timestamp":" 946891385880"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_121301"," gameId":" f8fed861-c7ec-49f9-9840-55c864b6a3bc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946891386014","data":{"timestamp":" 946891386014"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_121301"," gameId":" f8fed861-c7ec-49f9-9840-55c864b6a3bc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946891391736","data":{"timestamp":" 946891391736"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_121301"," gameId":" f8fed861-c7ec-49f9-9840-55c864b6a3bc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:100..1000.by.100.rand.s2s.AV.mc.83","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946891401413","data":{"timestamp":" 946891401412"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_121301"," gameId":" f8fed861-c7ec-49f9-9840-55c864b6a3bc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946891408270","data":{"timestamp":" 946891408270"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_121301"," gameId":" f8fed861-c7ec-49f9-9840-55c864b6a3bc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946891413785","data":{"timestamp":" 946891413785"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_121301"," gameId":" f8fed861-c7ec-49f9-9840-55c864b6a3bc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946891422181","data":{"timestamp":" 946891422180"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_121301"," gameId":" f8fed861-c7ec-49f9-9840-55c864b6a3bc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:100..1000.by.100.rand.s2s.AV.mc.83","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946891444847","data":{"timestamp":" 946891444846"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_121301"," gameId":" f8fed861-c7ec-49f9-9840-55c864b6a3bc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946891450303","data":{"timestamp":" 946891450303"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_121301"," gameId":" f8fed861-c7ec-49f9-9840-55c864b6a3bc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946891457297","data":{"timestamp":" 946891457297"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_121301"," gameId":" f8fed861-c7ec-49f9-9840-55c864b6a3bc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946891462415","data":{"timestamp":" 946891462414"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_121301"," gameId":" f8fed861-c7ec-49f9-9840-55c864b6a3bc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:100..1000.by.within.rand.s2s.AV.mc.84","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946891489901","data":{"timestamp":" 946891489901"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_121301"," gameId":" 6d765872-d28d-46e9-8e97-384218f5418c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_100..1000.by.within.rand.s2s.AV.mc.84"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_803_803-732-385"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 803"," userResponse":" 803"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:100..1000.by.within.rand.s2s.AV.mc.84","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946891504406","data":{"timestamp":" 946891504406"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_121301"," gameId":" 6d765872-d28d-46e9-8e97-384218f5418c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_100..1000.by.within.rand.s2s.AV.mc.84"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_693_803-693-154"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 693"," userResponse":" 803"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:100..1000.by.within.rand.s2s.AV.mc.84","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946891522486","data":{"timestamp":" 946891522486"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_121301"," gameId":" 6d765872-d28d-46e9-8e97-384218f5418c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_100..1000.by.within.rand.s2s.AV.mc.84"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_693_803-693-154"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 693"," userResponse":" 693"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:100..1000.by.within.rand.s2s.AV.mc.84","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946891527796","data":{"timestamp":" 946891527795"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_121301"," gameId":" 6d765872-d28d-46e9-8e97-384218f5418c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_100..1000.by.within.rand.s2s.AV.mc.84"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_693_803-693-154"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946891547690","data":{"timestamp":" 946891547690"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_121301"," gameId":" cdb12882-1c56-4c83-9005-1ad6c4246b32"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" WAKATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946891547810","data":{"timestamp":" 946891547810"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_121301"," gameId":" cdb12882-1c56-4c83-9005-1ad6c4246b32"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946891547995","data":{"timestamp":" 946891547995"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_121301"," gameId":" cdb12882-1c56-4c83-9005-1ad6c4246b32"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" WAKATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946891554523","data":{"timestamp":" 946891554523"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_121301"," gameId":" cdb12882-1c56-4c83-9005-1ad6c4246b32"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946891560887","data":{"timestamp":" 946891560887"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_121301"," gameId":" cdb12882-1c56-4c83-9005-1ad6c4246b32"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::100..1000.TD_OFFW100_DES.27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946891593525","data":{"timestamp":" 946891593525"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_121301"," gameId":" ee8b938a-c7b8-4aad-85ba-13c4ece7e2df"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__100..1000.TD_OFFW100_DES.27"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" elfu moja"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ELFU"," userResponse":" ELFU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::100..1000.TD_OFFW100_DES.27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946891595043","data":{"timestamp":" 946891595043"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_121301"," gameId":" ee8b938a-c7b8-4aad-85ba-13c4ece7e2df"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__100..1000.TD_OFFW100_DES.27"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" elfu moja"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::100..1000.TD_OFFW100_DES.27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946891603662","data":{"timestamp":" 946891603661"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_121301"," gameId":" ee8b938a-c7b8-4aad-85ba-13c4ece7e2df"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__100..1000.TD_OFFW100_DES.27"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" elfu moja"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ELFU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::100..1000.TD_OFFW100_DES.27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946891606527","data":{"timestamp":" 946891606527"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_121301"," gameId":" ee8b938a-c7b8-4aad-85ba-13c4ece7e2df"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__100..1000.TD_OFFW100_DES.27"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" elfu moja"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::100..1000.TD_OFFW100_DES.27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946891608842","data":{"timestamp":" 946891608842"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_121301"," gameId":" ee8b938a-c7b8-4aad-85ba-13c4ece7e2df"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__100..1000.TD_OFFW100_DES.27"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mia tisa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIA"," userResponse":" MIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::100..1000.TD_OFFW100_DES.27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946891610080","data":{"timestamp":" 946891610080"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_121301"," gameId":" ee8b938a-c7b8-4aad-85ba-13c4ece7e2df"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__100..1000.TD_OFFW100_DES.27"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mia tisa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TISA"," userResponse":" TISA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::100..1000.TD_OFFW100_DES.27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946891610592","data":{"timestamp":" 946891610592"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_121301"," gameId":" ee8b938a-c7b8-4aad-85ba-13c4ece7e2df"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__100..1000.TD_OFFW100_DES.27"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" mia tisa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946891610760","data":{"timestamp":" 946891610760"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_121301"," gameId":" ee8b938a-c7b8-4aad-85ba-13c4ece7e2df"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__100..1000.TD_OFFW100_DES.27"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mia tisa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TISA"," userResponse":" TISA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946891615776","data":{"timestamp":" 946891615776"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_121301"," gameId":" ee8b938a-c7b8-4aad-85ba-13c4ece7e2df"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__100..1000.TD_OFFW100_DES.27"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" mia tisa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946891630287","data":{"timestamp":" 946891630287"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_121301"," gameId":" 14e3b683-e30e-4efa-bdad-252c55868022"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946891630517","data":{"timestamp":" 946891630516"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_121301"," gameId":" 14e3b683-e30e-4efa-bdad-252c55868022"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946891630764","data":{"timestamp":" 946891630764"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_121301"," gameId":" 14e3b683-e30e-4efa-bdad-252c55868022"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946891630875","data":{"timestamp":" 946891630875"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_121301"," gameId":" 14e3b683-e30e-4efa-bdad-252c55868022"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946891636941","data":{"timestamp":" 946891636940"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_121301"," gameId":" 14e3b683-e30e-4efa-bdad-252c55868022"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.reveal::100..1000.TD_OFFW100_DES.54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946891655661","data":{"timestamp":" 946891655661"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_121301"," gameId":" ae2b0f6f-9837-41a4-a4f0-358b8c6a34a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.reveal__100..1000.TD_OFFW100_DES.54"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" elfu moja"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ELFU"," userResponse":" ELFU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.reveal::100..1000.TD_OFFW100_DES.54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946891661906","data":{"timestamp":" 946891661906"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_121301"," gameId":" ae2b0f6f-9837-41a4-a4f0-358b8c6a34a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.reveal__100..1000.TD_OFFW100_DES.54"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" elfu moja"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.reveal::100..1000.TD_OFFW100_DES.54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946891663072","data":{"timestamp":" 946891663072"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_121301"," gameId":" ae2b0f6f-9837-41a4-a4f0-358b8c6a34a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.reveal__100..1000.TD_OFFW100_DES.54"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" elfu moja"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946891663200","data":{"timestamp":" 946891663200"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_121301"," gameId":" ae2b0f6f-9837-41a4-a4f0-358b8c6a34a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.reveal__100..1000.TD_OFFW100_DES.54"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" elfu moja"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946891674279","data":{"timestamp":" 946891674279"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_121301"," gameId":" ae2b0f6f-9837-41a4-a4f0-358b8c6a34a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.reveal__100..1000.TD_OFFW100_DES.54"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" elfu moja"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946891680711","data":{"timestamp":" 946891680710"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_121301"," gameId":" ae2b0f6f-9837-41a4-a4f0-358b8c6a34a7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.reveal__100..1000.TD_OFFW100_DES.54"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" elfu moja"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946891698466","data":{"timestamp":" 946891698466"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_121301"," gameId":" c35ec0dd-a3bf-4e8b-ae2c-207e666b86fb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" START_WAKATI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946891700178","data":{"timestamp":" 946891700178"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_121301"," gameId":" c35ec0dd-a3bf-4e8b-ae2c-207e666b86fb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946891700335","data":{"timestamp":" 946891700334"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_121301"," gameId":" c35ec0dd-a3bf-4e8b-ae2c-207e666b86fb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" MMOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946891705551","data":{"timestamp":" 946891705551"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_121301"," gameId":" c35ec0dd-a3bf-4e8b-ae2c-207e666b86fb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" MMOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946891733910","data":{"timestamp":" 946891733910"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_121301"," gameId":" c35ec0dd-a3bf-4e8b-ae2c-207e666b86fb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946891759938","data":{"timestamp":" 946891759938"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_121301"," gameId":" 22104f4a-1738-4892-913d-611288867622"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_7"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kusoma kusoma"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSOMA"," userResponse":" KUSOMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946891760904","data":{"timestamp":" 946891760904"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_121301"," gameId":" 22104f4a-1738-4892-913d-611288867622"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_7"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kusoma kusoma"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSOMA"," userResponse":" KUSOMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946891763851","data":{"timestamp":" 946891763851"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_121301"," gameId":" 22104f4a-1738-4892-913d-611288867622"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_7"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunataka macho yaone"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNATAKA"," userResponse":" KUNATAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946891764385","data":{"timestamp":" 946891764385"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_121301"," gameId":" 22104f4a-1738-4892-913d-611288867622"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_7"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunataka macho yaone"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MACHO"," userResponse":" MACHO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946891765029","data":{"timestamp":" 946891765028"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_121301"," gameId":" 22104f4a-1738-4892-913d-611288867622"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_7"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunataka macho yaone"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAONE"," userResponse":" YAONE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946891769141","data":{"timestamp":" 946891769141"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_121301"," gameId":" 22104f4a-1738-4892-913d-611288867622"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_7"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Masikio yasikie"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MASIKIO"," userResponse":" MASIKIO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946891770076","data":{"timestamp":" 946891770076"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_121301"," gameId":" 22104f4a-1738-4892-913d-611288867622"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_7"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Masikio yasikie"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YASIKIE"," userResponse":" YASIKIE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946891773727","data":{"timestamp":" 946891773727"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_121301"," gameId":" 22104f4a-1738-4892-913d-611288867622"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_7"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na mdomo useme"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946891774511","data":{"timestamp":" 946891774511"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_121301"," gameId":" 22104f4a-1738-4892-913d-611288867622"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_7"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na mdomo useme"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MDOMO"," userResponse":" MDOMO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946891778967","data":{"timestamp":" 946891778966"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_121301"," gameId":" 22104f4a-1738-4892-913d-611288867622"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_7"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na mdomo useme"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" USEME"," userResponse":" USEME"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946891789938","data":{"timestamp":" 946891789938"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_121301"," gameId":" 22104f4a-1738-4892-913d-611288867622"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_7"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kusoma kusoma"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSOMA"," userResponse":" KUSOMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946891793375","data":{"timestamp":" 946891793375"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_121301"," gameId":" 22104f4a-1738-4892-913d-611288867622"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_7"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kusoma kusoma"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSOMA"," userResponse":" KUSOMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946891797535","data":{"timestamp":" 946891797535"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_121301"," gameId":" 22104f4a-1738-4892-913d-611288867622"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_7"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunataka macho yaone"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNATAKA"," userResponse":" KUNATAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946891798074","data":{"timestamp":" 946891798074"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_121301"," gameId":" 22104f4a-1738-4892-913d-611288867622"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_7"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunataka macho yaone"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MACHO"," userResponse":" MACHO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946891798738","data":{"timestamp":" 946891798737"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_121301"," gameId":" 22104f4a-1738-4892-913d-611288867622"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_7"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunataka macho yaone"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAONE"," userResponse":" YAONE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946891802835","data":{"timestamp":" 946891802835"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_121301"," gameId":" 22104f4a-1738-4892-913d-611288867622"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_7"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Masikio yasikie"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MASIKIO"," userResponse":" MASIKIO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946891803777","data":{"timestamp":" 946891803776"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_121301"," gameId":" 22104f4a-1738-4892-913d-611288867622"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_7"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Masikio yasikie"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YASIKIE"," userResponse":" YASIKIE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946891807426","data":{"timestamp":" 946891807426"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_121301"," gameId":" 22104f4a-1738-4892-913d-611288867622"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_7"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na mdomo useme"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946891808212","data":{"timestamp":" 946891808212"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_121301"," gameId":" 22104f4a-1738-4892-913d-611288867622"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_7"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na mdomo useme"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MDOMO"," userResponse":" MDOMO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946891811860","data":{"timestamp":" 946891811860"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_121301"," gameId":" 22104f4a-1738-4892-913d-611288867622"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_7"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na mdomo useme"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" USEME"," userResponse":" USEME"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946891817587","data":{"timestamp":" 946891817587"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_121301"," gameId":" 22104f4a-1738-4892-913d-611288867622"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_7"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Na mdomo useme"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946891817710","data":{"timestamp":" 946891817709"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_121301"," gameId":" 22104f4a-1738-4892-913d-611288867622"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_7"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na mdomo useme"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" USEME"," userResponse":" USEME"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946891829526","data":{"timestamp":" 946891829526"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_121301"," gameId":" 22104f4a-1738-4892-913d-611288867622"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_7"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Na mdomo useme"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946891835291","data":{"timestamp":" 946891835290"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_121301"," gameId":" 22104f4a-1738-4892-913d-611288867622"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_7"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Na mdomo useme"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946891841128","data":{"timestamp":" 946891841128"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_121301"," gameId":" 22104f4a-1738-4892-913d-611288867622"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_7"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Na mdomo useme"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:3d.by.hun","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946891886271","data":{"timestamp":" 946891886271"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_121301"," gameId":" 5e9eb54e-1125-4cc2-bf83-584b5977cd94"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_3d.by.hun"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_200v300"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 300"," userResponse":" 300"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:3d.by.hun","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946891886501","data":{"timestamp":" 946891886500"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_121301"," gameId":" 5e9eb54e-1125-4cc2-bf83-584b5977cd94"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_3d.by.hun"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_200v300"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 300"," userResponse":" 300"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:3d.by.hun","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946891886696","data":{"timestamp":" 946891886696"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_121301"," gameId":" 5e9eb54e-1125-4cc2-bf83-584b5977cd94"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_3d.by.hun"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_200v300"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 300"," userResponse":" 300"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:3d.by.hun","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946891886883","data":{"timestamp":" 946891886883"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_121301"," gameId":" 5e9eb54e-1125-4cc2-bf83-584b5977cd94"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_3d.by.hun"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_200v300"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 300"," userResponse":" 300"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:3d.by.hun","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946891887707","data":{"timestamp":" 946891887707"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_121301"," gameId":" 5e9eb54e-1125-4cc2-bf83-584b5977cd94"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_3d.by.hun"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_200v300"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 300"," userResponse":" 300"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:3d.by.hun","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946891890810","data":{"timestamp":" 946891890810"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_121301"," gameId":" 5e9eb54e-1125-4cc2-bf83-584b5977cd94"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_3d.by.hun"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_100v400"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 400"," userResponse":" 400"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:3d.by.hun","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946891901044","data":{"timestamp":" 946891901044"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_121301"," gameId":" 5e9eb54e-1125-4cc2-bf83-584b5977cd94"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_3d.by.hun"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_100v400"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 400"," userResponse":" 400"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:3d.by.hun","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946891901044","data":{"timestamp":" 946891901044"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_121301"," gameId":" 5e9eb54e-1125-4cc2-bf83-584b5977cd94"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_3d.by.hun"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_100v400"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 400"," userResponse":" 400"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:3d.by.hun","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946891903842","data":{"timestamp":" 946891903842"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_121301"," gameId":" 5e9eb54e-1125-4cc2-bf83-584b5977cd94"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_3d.by.hun"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_400v300"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 400"," userResponse":" 400"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:3d.by.hun","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946891925968","data":{"timestamp":" 946891925968"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_121301"," gameId":" 5e9eb54e-1125-4cc2-bf83-584b5977cd94"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_3d.by.hun"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_400v300"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 400"," userResponse":" 400"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:3d.by.hun","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946891925969","data":{"timestamp":" 946891925969"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_121301"," gameId":" 5e9eb54e-1125-4cc2-bf83-584b5977cd94"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_3d.by.hun"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_400v300"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 400"," userResponse":" 400"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:3d.by.hun","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946891929725","data":{"timestamp":" 946891929725"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_121301"," gameId":" 5e9eb54e-1125-4cc2-bf83-584b5977cd94"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_3d.by.hun"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_400v300"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 400"," userResponse":" 400"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:3d.by.hun","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946891931272","data":{"timestamp":" 946891931272"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_121301"," gameId":" 5e9eb54e-1125-4cc2-bf83-584b5977cd94"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_3d.by.hun"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_400v300"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 400"," userResponse":" 400"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:3d.by.hun","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946891936624","data":{"timestamp":" 946891936624"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_121301"," gameId":" 5e9eb54e-1125-4cc2-bf83-584b5977cd94"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_3d.by.hun"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_300v100"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 300"," userResponse":" 300"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:3d.by.hun","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946891940711","data":{"timestamp":" 946891940711"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_121301"," gameId":" 5e9eb54e-1125-4cc2-bf83-584b5977cd94"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_3d.by.hun"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_200v300"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 300"," userResponse":" 300"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:3d.by.hun","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946891942326","data":{"timestamp":" 946891942326"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_121301"," gameId":" 5e9eb54e-1125-4cc2-bf83-584b5977cd94"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_3d.by.hun"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_200v300"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 300"," userResponse":" 300"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:3d.by.hun","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946891945716","data":{"timestamp":" 946891945716"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_121301"," gameId":" 5e9eb54e-1125-4cc2-bf83-584b5977cd94"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_3d.by.hun"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_100v400"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 400"," userResponse":" 400"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:3d.by.hun","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946891947305","data":{"timestamp":" 946891947305"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_121301"," gameId":" 5e9eb54e-1125-4cc2-bf83-584b5977cd94"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_3d.by.hun"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_100v400"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 400"," userResponse":" 400"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:3d.by.hun","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946891953899","data":{"timestamp":" 946891953898"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_121301"," gameId":" 5e9eb54e-1125-4cc2-bf83-584b5977cd94"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_3d.by.hun"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_100v400"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 400"," userResponse":" 400"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:3d.by.hun","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946891959065","data":{"timestamp":" 946891959064"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_121301"," gameId":" 5e9eb54e-1125-4cc2-bf83-584b5977cd94"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_3d.by.hun"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_200v300"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 300"," userResponse":" 300"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:3d.by.hun","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946891959319","data":{"timestamp":" 946891959319"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_121301"," gameId":" 5e9eb54e-1125-4cc2-bf83-584b5977cd94"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_3d.by.hun"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_200v300"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 300"," userResponse":" 300"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:3d.by.hun","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946891959566","data":{"timestamp":" 946891959566"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_121301"," gameId":" 5e9eb54e-1125-4cc2-bf83-584b5977cd94"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_3d.by.hun"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_200v300"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 300"," userResponse":" 300"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:3d.by.hun","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946891961014","data":{"timestamp":" 946891961014"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_121301"," gameId":" 5e9eb54e-1125-4cc2-bf83-584b5977cd94"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_3d.by.hun"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" ND_200v300"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946891981825","data":{"timestamp":" 946891981825"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_121301"," gameId":" a555373a-95c5-4dcb-8e06-f5ccec14f429"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" WAKATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946892012076","data":{"timestamp":" 946892012076"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_121301"," gameId":" a555373a-95c5-4dcb-8e06-f5ccec14f429"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946892013899","data":{"timestamp":" 946892013899"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_121301"," gameId":" a555373a-95c5-4dcb-8e06-f5ccec14f429"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946892014089","data":{"timestamp":" 946892014089"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_121301"," gameId":" a555373a-95c5-4dcb-8e06-f5ccec14f429"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946892019966","data":{"timestamp":" 946892019966"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_121301"," gameId":" a555373a-95c5-4dcb-8e06-f5ccec14f429"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946892038126","data":{"timestamp":" 946892038126"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_121301"," gameId":" a57af601-b47a-433c-aaab-7638e6745fbb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946892042794","data":{"timestamp":" 946892042794"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_121301"," gameId":" a57af601-b47a-433c-aaab-7638e6745fbb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" START_MMOJA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946892050705","data":{"timestamp":" 946892050705"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_121301"," gameId":" a57af601-b47a-433c-aaab-7638e6745fbb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946892050837","data":{"timestamp":" 946892050837"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_121301"," gameId":" a57af601-b47a-433c-aaab-7638e6745fbb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" START_MMOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:num.100..900.GL_DD_OFF100_M.bub2.29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946892062653","data":{"timestamp":" 946892062653"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_121301"," gameId":" a57af601-b47a-433c-aaab-7638e6745fbb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946892074204","data":{"timestamp":" 946892074204"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_121301"," gameId":" a57af601-b47a-433c-aaab-7638e6745fbb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946892081077","data":{"timestamp":" 946892081077"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_121301"," gameId":" a57af601-b47a-433c-aaab-7638e6745fbb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946892088138","data":{"timestamp":" 946892088138"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_121301"," gameId":" a57af601-b47a-433c-aaab-7638e6745fbb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:num.100..900.GL_DD_OFF100_M.bub2.29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946892138125","data":{"timestamp":" 946892138125"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_121301"," gameId":" 8578f0c4-8871-441a-92d6-619f994e83cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_num.100..900.GL_DD_OFF100_M.bub2.29"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_825_825-725"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 825"," userResponse":" 825"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:num.100..900.GL_DD_OFF100_M.bub2.29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946892147154","data":{"timestamp":" 946892147154"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_121301"," gameId":" 8578f0c4-8871-441a-92d6-619f994e83cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_num.100..900.GL_DD_OFF100_M.bub2.29"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_863_863-763"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 863"," userResponse":" 863"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:num.100..900.GL_DD_OFF100_M.bub2.29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946892156956","data":{"timestamp":" 946892156956"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_121301"," gameId":" 8578f0c4-8871-441a-92d6-619f994e83cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_num.100..900.GL_DD_OFF100_M.bub2.29"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_208_108-208"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 208"," userResponse":" 208"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:num.100..900.GL_DD_OFF100_M.bub2.29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946892165582","data":{"timestamp":" 946892165581"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_121301"," gameId":" 8578f0c4-8871-441a-92d6-619f994e83cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_num.100..900.GL_DD_OFF100_M.bub2.29"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_951_951-851"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 951"," userResponse":" 951"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:num.100..900.GL_DD_OFF100_M.bub2.29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946892175538","data":{"timestamp":" 946892175538"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_121301"," gameId":" 8578f0c4-8871-441a-92d6-619f994e83cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_num.100..900.GL_DD_OFF100_M.bub2.29"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_354_354-254"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 354"," userResponse":" 354"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:num.100..900.GL_DD_OFF100_M.bub2.29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946892183878","data":{"timestamp":" 946892183877"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_121301"," gameId":" 8578f0c4-8871-441a-92d6-619f994e83cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_num.100..900.GL_DD_OFF100_M.bub2.29"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_958_958-858"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 958"," userResponse":" 958"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:num.100..900.GL_DD_OFF100_M.bub2.29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946892192130","data":{"timestamp":" 946892192130"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_121301"," gameId":" 8578f0c4-8871-441a-92d6-619f994e83cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_num.100..900.GL_DD_OFF100_M.bub2.29"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_680_580-680"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 680"," userResponse":" 680"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:num.100..900.GL_DD_OFF100_M.bub2.29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946892201083","data":{"timestamp":" 946892201083"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_121301"," gameId":" 8578f0c4-8871-441a-92d6-619f994e83cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_num.100..900.GL_DD_OFF100_M.bub2.29"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_920_820-920"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 920"," userResponse":" 920"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:num.100..900.GL_DD_OFF100_M.bub2.29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946892211017","data":{"timestamp":" 946892211017"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_121301"," gameId":" 8578f0c4-8871-441a-92d6-619f994e83cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_num.100..900.GL_DD_OFF100_M.bub2.29"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_350_350-250"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 350"," userResponse":" 350"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:num.100..900.GL_DD_OFF100_M.bub2.29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946892219849","data":{"timestamp":" 946892219849"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_121301"," gameId":" 8578f0c4-8871-441a-92d6-619f994e83cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_num.100..900.GL_DD_OFF100_M.bub2.29"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_363_363-263"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 363"," userResponse":" 363"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:num.100..900.GL_DD_OFF100_M.bub2.29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946892229570","data":{"timestamp":" 946892229570"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_121301"," gameId":" 8578f0c4-8871-441a-92d6-619f994e83cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_num.100..900.GL_DD_OFF100_M.bub2.29"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_363_363-263"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946892234986","data":{"timestamp":" 946892234985"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_121301"," gameId":" 8578f0c4-8871-441a-92d6-619f994e83cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_num.100..900.GL_DD_OFF100_M.bub2.29"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_363_363-263"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946892240492","data":{"timestamp":" 946892240492"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_121301"," gameId":" 8578f0c4-8871-441a-92d6-619f994e83cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_num.100..900.GL_DD_OFF100_M.bub2.29"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_363_363-263"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946892245936","data":{"timestamp":" 946892245932"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_121301"," gameId":" 8578f0c4-8871-441a-92d6-619f994e83cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_num.100..900.GL_DD_OFF100_M.bub2.29"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_363_363-263"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:num.100..900.GL_DD_OFF100_L.bub2.30","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946892256111","data":{"timestamp":" 946892256111"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_121301"," gameId":" 8578f0c4-8871-441a-92d6-619f994e83cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_num.100..900.GL_DD_OFF100_M.bub2.29"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_363_363-263"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946892265999","data":{"timestamp":" 946892265999"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_121301"," gameId":" 8578f0c4-8871-441a-92d6-619f994e83cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_num.100..900.GL_DD_OFF100_M.bub2.29"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_363_363-263"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946892273318","data":{"timestamp":" 946892273317"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_121301"," gameId":" 8578f0c4-8871-441a-92d6-619f994e83cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_num.100..900.GL_DD_OFF100_M.bub2.29"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_363_363-263"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946892282257","data":{"timestamp":" 946892282257"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_121301"," gameId":" 8578f0c4-8871-441a-92d6-619f994e83cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_num.100..900.GL_DD_OFF100_M.bub2.29"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_363_363-263"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:3d.by.ten","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946892294425","data":{"timestamp":" 946892294424"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_121301"," gameId":" 8578f0c4-8871-441a-92d6-619f994e83cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_num.100..900.GL_DD_OFF100_M.bub2.29"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_363_363-263"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946892300789","data":{"timestamp":" 946892300789"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_121301"," gameId":" 8578f0c4-8871-441a-92d6-619f994e83cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_num.100..900.GL_DD_OFF100_M.bub2.29"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_363_363-263"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946892308267","data":{"timestamp":" 946892308266"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_121301"," gameId":" 8578f0c4-8871-441a-92d6-619f994e83cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_num.100..900.GL_DD_OFF100_M.bub2.29"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_363_363-263"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946892315193","data":{"timestamp":" 946892315192"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_121301"," gameId":" 8578f0c4-8871-441a-92d6-619f994e83cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_num.100..900.GL_DD_OFF100_M.bub2.29"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_363_363-263"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}